MLK had been a very prim and proper Negro.
However, in Where Do We Go From Here, Community or Chaos,
the last book he wrote before being assassinated
on that fateful balcony in Memphis, Tennessee,
he laments that a year after the Voting Rights Act had passed,
though the law changed,
the American sentiment toward the Negro had not.
This was the burning house that MLK Jr. feared
he'd integrated his people into.
We're so often sold a version of Dr. King
that is palatable to the oppressor.
One that depicts him as like an obedient subject,
passively asking for their rights on bended knees,
like, please, sir, I'm all right, sir.
Rather than forcefully demanding them,
when in actuality, he was only 26
at the start of the Montgomery boycott.
And by his death, he was 39.
You know how much you change in that amount of time.
Like, I was dating drug dealers at 26.
I still was at 39.
MLK may have started seeking integration.
He eventually saw through the guys
and understood that it was capitalism
that was allowing racism to subsist.
He began to support the labor unions.
He questioned government allocation of resources.
He advocated for reparations.
Where are we cutting the check?
It was after all of this,
when he had evolved into Martin Luther,
the king,
that this nation thought to be rid of him.
I want you to know that you can check out
the full two and a half hour show
by heading on over to Patreon, Amanda Seals.
That's right.
Patreon.com backslash Amanda Seals
gives you two options.
One, you can purchase the unlimited access
to the live stream,
or two, for just $5 less,
you can subscribe to the Hello Ancestors tier
and not only get unlimited access to the live stream,
but also get unlimited access
to the Seals Squad community.
And don't forget,
What Would the Ancestors Say?
is now also available as a book and in other forms.
So go to amandalandexports.com
or amandaseals.com and show your love.